<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>FOSSAssam</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on FOSSAssam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 19:02:31 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2nd Meet - Hacktoberfest Ghy 2019</title>
      <link>/post/hof-meet2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2019 19:02:31 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hof-meet2/</guid>
      <description>Registration link: bit.ly/hof-ghy-2ndmu-reg Hacktoberfest link: hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com/ Code of Conduct  The first meetup was a success, so we&amp;rsquo;re following up with another meetup on (26th October 2019, Saturday), will be posting a blogpost describing the first meeup very soon!
Hello everyone! 🎊 Welcome to the 2nd Meet of Hacktoberfest Guwahati. This page is dedicated for describing the agenda of the offline Hacktoberfest Guwahati meetup on 26th October (Saturday) to be organized at Institute of Science &amp;amp; Technology (GUIST), Guwahati.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMA with Ashris Choudhary - Hacktoberfest&#39;19</title>
      <link>/post/ama-ashris/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 12:57:13 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/ama-ashris/</guid>
      <description>This year during Hactoberfest we decided to run a month-long study group in the form a WhatsApp group.
I read the following somewhere, this makes perfect sense to be applied to this study group:
 The formula to induce motivation, in my experience, starts with action, which sparks inspiration, which sparks motivation, which leads to action, and the loop continues.
 So we decided to have WhatsApp AMAs in the group, which turned out to be a super fine idea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacktoberfest Ghy 2019</title>
      <link>/post/hacktoberfest-ghy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2019 10:44:38 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/hacktoberfest-ghy/</guid>
      <description>Registration link: bit.ly/hof-ghy-reg Hacktoberfest link: hacktoberfest.digitalocean.com/ Code of Conduct  Hello everyone! 🎊 Welcome to Hacktoberfest Guwahati. This page is dedicated for describing the agenda of the offline Hacktoberfest Guwahati meetup on 19th October (Saturday) to be organized at Royal Global University, Guwahati.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a short intro about Hacktoberfest for who are not familiar. If you already know what this is all about, directly skip to the Agenda section:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrapping up TF All Around Guwahati</title>
      <link>/post/tf-aa-rgu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 21:46:52 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tf-aa-rgu/</guid>
      <description>The FossAssam team along with the speakers for the event had a great time organizing Tensorflow All Around Guwahati on 14th September&amp;rsquo;19 at Royal Global University. We had around ~50 enthusiastic participants out of ~100 that registered. Thanks to RGU for providing an excellent venue for the event.
The goal was to introduce newcomers to Machine Learning and Tensorflow and show what it is like to use Machine learning in the Industry for people who are already working with these concepts and technologies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TensorFlow All Around - Guwahati</title>
      <link>/post/tf-ghy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 16:59:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tf-ghy/</guid>
      <description>Registration Link: bit.ly/tf-ghy-rgu
 Hello everyone! 🎊 Good news for every computer science student and machine learning enthusiast in Guwahati. Very excited to announce that we&amp;rsquo;ll be organizing TensorFlow All Around in Guwahati.
TensorFlow All Around is a global series of community-led events, where developers can learn the essentials and best practices of TensorFlow.
Join us for the TensorFlow All-Around event and get hands-on experience with TensorFlow together! After this event you can keep developing your skills at home by completing all the recommended codelab, tutorials and videos.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>